Guide to the E. Raymond Hall Collection
University of Kansas
- PP 513
  - (Box Box 4)
    - Staff mtg. [meeting] minutes, course materials, notes (Folder 19)
    - Museum monthly mtg [meeting] (Folder 20)
    - Nat[ural] Hist[ory] Mus[eum] related, Hillsdale Reservoir Army Corps (Folder 21)
    - US Army Corps of Engineer - Tract no. [number] 335 (Folder 22)
    - Salary misc[ellaneous] Hillsdale (Folder 23)
    - Hillsdale Trial - Hamilton misc[ellaneous] (Folder 24)
    - Tract no [number] 335 - Hillsdale Lake Prg [program] (Folder 25)
    - Hillsdale Trial, Hamilton, Humphreys (Folder 26)
    - Hillsdale Trial, Hamilton, Humphreys (Folder 27)
    - Hillsdale Trial, Hamilton, Humphreys (Folder 28)
    - Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 29)
    - Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 30)
    - Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 31)
    - Museum of Natural History, Dept [department] of Zoology, group picture 1962-[19]63, Sept[ember] 1962 Faculty of Zoology (Folder 32)
  - (Box Box 5 (Oversized))
    - Oversized photograph removed from Box 2 (Folder 1)